Yes, I am now in a haunted house with an altitude of 3000 meters! Yeah!
What's that? There's an alien over there! Yoo-hoo!
I like big eyes!
Okay, so I'm going to try my hand at a live video game in this haunted house now!
I'm not like that!
Nighttime and Idol!
Come on!
Kanakasanho-san has an announcement!
Yes! Do you have it?
Yes, yes!
Yes, please!
We, Clanpop, are going to have a one-on-one live performance at Shinjuku Renny on Sunday, April 23rd,
We, Clanpop, are going to have a one-on-one live performance at Shinjuku Lenny on Sunday, April 23rd!
Yay!
We are looking forward to it!
Yes, there is more to come,
From September to December
We are going to have a hashtag KURAPOKKAWAII national spread tour from September to December!
Yay!
We will be visiting everyone from Hokkaido in the north to Okinawa in the south so that we can fill the whole country with Kurapokka Waii.
And one more thing, on Thursday, December 28th
We will be doing a revenge sandku live at Krumpop JUP DIVERSITY on Thursday, December 28th!
Yay!
I see!
That's a lot of fun, isn't it, this time around?
Yes!
Yes, I do.
Well, there are a lot of events coming up,
Well, I couldn't quite grasp the actual state of Mr. Tanaka today.
Really?
Well, I guess that's the charm of this place.
And so, I would like to give you a gift of tea to cheer you up,
May I? Do you drink tea?
Yes, I do. May I?
I have prepared jasmine tea for you today!
Thank you very much. It's very relaxing.
Yes, it is.
Yes, it is. I haven't had jasmine tea very often.
Jasmine tea relaxes me.
I don't know, I can't feel your heart in every word you say.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no. It's amazing, isn't it? But you are drawn into it, really.
I'm really drawn into it.
Don't people say that at benefit events?
Like, "Oh no, you don't have a heart, Mr. Tanaka.
No, they don't.
Oh, you don't?
I probably wouldn't say it even if I thought it.
Oh, I see. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Yes, it is. Please drink it.
Bon appétit.
Mmm. Mmm.
Huh? What is it? It tastes like jasmine tea.
But it tastes good.
Easy to drink jasmine tea.
Oh, I see.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Well, I'm an honest person.
I'll make you some. It's delicious.
You don't want to tell me.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's... it's... it's... it's... it's... it's...
It's so much lighter.
It tastes like it's going down your throat.
Yes.
I don't know, it's hard to describe.
I'm not good at food reports.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's like you don't have a heart.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wow.
It's delicious.
No, but I got it.
Thank you.
Why are you leaving?
Each one of your reactions is what I like about you.
Thank you very much.
Now, may I finish? May I have this?
Yes.
Let's end this show in a cute, idol-like way!
May I ask you to face the camera?
Pretty? Oh, my God, what am I going to do?
Closing? I've never done much closing.
I've never done it before, but I think it raises the bar when you're messing around with it.
Okay, the letters are great.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
So, I hope you enjoy the next installment of Yakanta Idol!
That's all for now, this is Saho Tanaka of Crown Pop! Bye bye!
See you soon!
This program is brought to you by
This program was brought to you by
Thank you very much!
See you next time!
What? But it's the fifth time.
That's the last one. See you later.